Okay so let's start on the nose, it's a shadow, that was a mix of, let's just oil in, a bit of oil,
on your brush, turn that off, you need to shape the underside of that nose,
bring it up a bit higher, then I think it was red and tumble,
you're just fixing that profile nose there, just fixing some of these shapes to start off with,
okay, then we're going to pick out the nostril, here's an ivory, that's purple, burnt umber,
okay, then I'm going to work into this, make this a bit more solid, okay, then pick out the
some of the ivory, pick out the reflected light, just a bit more red, to the burnt umber,
okay, some of the corner, the nose is some reflected light, so that a bit more solid, that was a red,
a red like a mid violet, okay red, touch a full, okay, we'll work this edge,
it's transition, we're going to push that edge back down at some point, the um looks like the nose,
maybe I'll touch it orange, red, purple, pick out this, yeah I'll leave that, all right,
just looking around here, there's a bit of light penumbra, that side there, then around the lip,
it gets a bit cooler, purple in there, there's a bit more that are inside of the corner,
it's underneath here, it's going to be a bit lighter, going to put that shape in there and pick out that
lighter shape after, okay, now I'm looking for the highlights, hierarchy of highlights,
that nose, something, think about that junction, okay, then the next highlight, clean your brush,
so there's going to be some yellow, a bit of orange in there, okay, then just around here,
bridge the nose, light, okay, I'm just going to turn that highlight down a bit,
look for the bridge of the nose, turn around the bridge there, kind of lighten up, shape around
that highlight, looking down this edge, gets a bit lighter, towards the highlight,
on this edge here, pink side, lighten up around this highlight here, so yeah just lighten up these
shapes around the highlight there, okay, then look at finishing off, just start with that brow,
shape first on the illiterate side, yellow, touch of green, neutralise that,
too much green, and then we're just going to work back in to this stuff, it's the brow there,
you can call that the brow, get the nose, it gets a bit darker, it turns away,
and then look at the side plane of the nose, okay, so we divide the side plane of the nose
into the nostril shape there, then got this shape here, got the maxilla,
plane of the maxilla, it's slightly warmer around the bottom of the nose, so maybe
touch more yellow in there, touch of green, blow the chroma, okay now I can suffer this edge,
then you've got the inside of the shape here, pretty dark enough, and I'll just lighten the
maxilla, lighter, alizarin, okay, lighten this shape here, all right so I'm going to pick out the
nostril, and that's just almost the lighter version, okay, take some of this red, the nose,
okay, then I'm going to divide the shape in here, okay so just underneath this
I'll probably shape there, it's a bit lighter, a bit more darker than that, a bit of
yellow in there, that shape in there, okay, brown plane of the nose, look at that,
a bit more, a bit cooler, and there putting more on the violet side, like that orange,
okay, just lighten that around the highlight,
edge of the nose, it turns away, a bit more on the violet side, too dark, okay, I'm going to call that the nose done.